Guide to the Agnes Boulton Collection of Eugene O'Neill
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Personal Papers, 1912-1949; Series III; 0.60' (2 boxes)
  - FINANCIAL AND LEGAL MATERIALS
    - National Institute of Arts and Letters. Bills for dues for, 1924, 1926 (Box 6, Folder 178)
    - O'Neill, Eugene. Medical expenses for, 1922-26 (Box 6, Folder 179)
    - O'Neill, Eugene, Jr. Medical expenses for (Box 6, Folder 180)
    - O'Neill, James, Jr. Medical expense for, 1923 Nov 1 (Box 6, Folder 181)
    - O'Neill, Mary Ellen Quinlan. Bill for tax on estate of, 1923 (Box 6, Folder 182)
    - Peaked Hill Bar (Provincetown, Mass.). Bill for taxes on, 1925 Oct 1 (Box 6, Folder 183)
    - Spithead (Bermuda Islands). Legal documents (photostats) regarding, 1926-49 (Box 6, Folder 184)
    - Telegrams. Bills for, 1924-28 (Box 6, Folder 185)
  - PHOTOGRAPHS
    - Eugene O'Neill
      - Wearing [underwear?], standing indoors, [ca. 1912] (Box 6, Folder 186)
      - Wearing bathing suit, standing in water, [ca. 1912] (Box 6, Folder 187)
      - Wearing bathing suit, standing in front of fence, [ca. 1912] (Box 6, Folder 187)
      - Sitting on steps of 34 Pequot Avenue with Marion Welch, [ca. 1912] (Box 6, Folder 188)
      - Wearing bathing suit, sitting in boat with unidentified woman and unidentified man, [ca. 1914] (Box 6, Folder 189)
      - Standing in front of [gazebo?], [ca. 1915] (Box 6, Folder 190)
    - Other
      - Ben (Irish setter dog). Lying in driveway, Château du Plessis (St. Antoine-du-Rocher, Indre et Loire, France), [1930] (Box 6, Folder 191)
        Inscribed on back by EO.
      - Château du Plessis (St. Antoine-du- Rocher, Indre et Loire, France). View of drive, [1930] (Box 6, Folder 192)
      - Clark, Fifine. Standing on porch, [192-] (Box 6, Folder 193)
        Inscribed by Clark to Shane Rudraighe O'Neill.
      - Millay, Kathleen. Leaning on fence, [192-] (Box 6, Folder 194)
        Inscribed on back to EO and AB from "H. I. Y and annotated."
      - Silverdene Emblem (dalmation dog). Lying in driveway at Château du Plessis (St. Antoine-du-Rocher, Indre et Loire, France), [1930] (Box 6, Folder 195)
- Restricted Fragile Papers, 0.20' (1 box)
  Box 7, Restricted Fragile, contains fragile originals. The material is arranged in folder order and may only be seen with the permission of the appropriate curator. Preservation photocopies or photographic prints have been substituted in the main files for reference use.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted fragile material. Reference surrogates have been substituted in the main files. For further information consult the appropriate curator.
  - Box 1, folder 3 (Box 7, Folder 196)
  - Box 1, folder 5 (Box 7, Folder 197)
  - Box 1, folder 23 (Box 7, Folder 198)
  - Box 1, folder 48 (Box 7, Folder 199)
  - Box 1, folder 50 (Box 7, Folder 200)
  - Box 1, folder 53 (Box 7, Folder 201)
  - Box 1, folder 59 (Box 7, Folder 202)
  - Box 1, folder 63 (Box 7, Folder 203)
  - Box 2, folder 71 (Box 7, Folder 204)
  - Box 2, folder 73 (Box 7, Folder 205)
  - Box 2, folder 93 (Box 7, Folder 206)
  - Box 2, folder 99 (Box 7, Folder 207)
  - Box 2, folder 110 (Box 7, Folder 208)
  - Box 2, folder 118 (Box 7, Folder 209)
  - Box 2, folder 122 (Box 7, Folder 210)
  - Box 2, folder 124 (Box 7, Folder 211)
  - Box 2, folder 127 (Box 7, Folder 212)
  - Box 3, folder 129 (Box 7, Folder 213)
  - Box 3, folder 137 (Box 7, Folder 214)
  - Box 4, folder 167 (Box 7, Folder 215)